<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:src="@drawable/background"
    tools:context=".Agreement">


    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_width="266dp"
        android:layout_height="42dp"
        android:background="@drawable/filedsset"
        android:text="Privacy and policy"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="@color/text"
        android:textSize="30sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.062" />

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/button"
        android:layout_width="152dp"
        android:layout_height="57dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="4dp"
        android:background="@drawable/filedsset"
        android:onClick="onButton_BeginClick"
        android:text="Begin"
        android:textColor="@color/text"

        android:textSize="24sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.942"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.982" />

    <CheckBox
        android:id="@+id/checkBox"
        android:layout_width="274dp"
        android:layout_height="45dp"
        android:layout_gravity="start"
        android:layout_marginBottom="72dp"
        android:layoutDirection="rtl"
        android:text="I accept,and want to continue"
        android:textAlignment="textStart"
        android:textSize="18sp"
        android:buttonTint="#292150"
        android:textColor="#292150"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.905"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.998" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="358dp"
        android:layout_height="357dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="120dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.47"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.198">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView28"
                android:layout_width="360dp"
                android:layout_height="1500dp"
                android:text='  We welcome you on mobile app "Baby in danger" .
                This agreement discloses the terms in accordance with which the client may use our on-line services, website and software (in aggregate - “Service). Upon receiving an access to the services or by using it the client hereby agrees on the fact that he/she is fully aware, acknowledge and accept all terms of the present Terms of Services Use agreement (hereinafter – “Agreement”). The present agreement is applied for all potential visitors, clients and other users who use the services (hereinafter – “Users”).  Terms of service use is a document that constitutes a public offer i.e an offer to conclude a license agreement providing a right to access and use of the service.  In case you disagree to these terms please do not click “Continue” button and avoid further use of our services. Following the good faith principals and pursue one’s own interests by clicking “Continue” button (public offer acceptance) you automatically accept and agree with all terms of this agreement and its supplements (acceptance means full understanding and unquestioning) and conclude this license agreement with the service management in accordance with the terms specified in the present offer.  Any kind of disputes based on the unawareness claims as to existence of the terms right after acceptance of the present agreement cannot be accepted or reviewed anyhow.  In the event that You accept this public offer, there is a license agreement between You and the Licensor under conditions of this public offer. If You purchase other services, there is a mixed contract, containing the elements of a license agreement and a service agreement.   1. Services use  Our service is created in order to rest parents assured for their children.    The service is meant to be used by the citizens of United States of America, Europe Union, Russian Federation countries. Please note that some service features might not be available for use outside the GPS area and wireless data transmission for the phone/device the app is installed on.  2. Service regulations  The client is not allowed to: (i) copy, publish or disclose any part of the Service in any media including but not limited to automated or non-automated “duplication”; (ii) use any kind of automated system including apart from everything else “robots” and any of its kind in order to access the Service in a manner allowing to send the multiple requests to the Company’s servers rather than an individual can send within the same timeframe using an ordinary web browser; (iii) send spam, letters thread or any other unsuitable content; (iv) disrupt attempts, discredit the system integrity or its security or decipher the data transmitted to the server or from the servers on which the service is on at; (v) take any actions which can be considered by the Company as ones leading or might be leading to disproportionate or meaningless heavy infrastructure load; (vi) upload an invalid data, viruses, worms or any other software bots by means of the Service; (vii) collect any personal data including the profile names stored in Service; (viii) perform non-commercial use of the Service; (ix) take on a different persona or in any other way falsify the belonging to a particular individual or a legal entity, commit a fraud, hide or try to conceal your true identity; (x) affect the proper Service work; (xi) access to any content in frames of the Service using any technology or any other methods beside ones allowed or offered by the Service; or bypassing the measures which can be taken in order to prevent or limit the access to the Service, including but not limited to the features preventing or limiting the usage or copying of any content or set the limits on the Service or its content use.  In accordance with the terms of the present Agreement the Client is offered with an unexceptional, easy-in-use, non-transferable, an easy-revoking license allowing the Service use with the purpose of personal, non-commercial use and in accordance to the possibilities of the Service. The Company reserves the  right to terminate such a license at any time and at its sole discretion.  The profiles created during the Service use allow you to access to the services and features which can be expanded and maintained at the Company’s sole discretion. Upon the profile creation you must provide the actual and detailed information. The Client bears full responsibility for all actions taken in frames of profile as well as keep all the personal data confidential. The Client shall promptly give notice to the Company of any security violation or any unauthorized use of the Client profile. The Company is not liable for any potential losses caused by any unauthorized use of the Client personal profile.  The Client has the right to manage his/her personal profile and the way how one interacts with the Service by changing the available settings.  3. Mobile software  Within frames of the Service the Company offers the mobile software and/or apps developed for the mobile devices use (hereinafter – “Mobile software”). In order to use a mobile software, the Client must have a mobile device compatible with Mobile software. The Company does not guarantee that Mobile software is fully compatible with the device the Clients has. Hereby the Company grants the Client an unexceptional, non-transferrable, revocable license allowing to use a compiled coded copy of Mobile software per one registered profile that belongs or loaned exclusively by the Client for the personal use only.  The Client is not allowed to: (i) modify, decompile or reconstruct the Mobile software; (ii) sublicense and spread or otherwise provide any other third party with an access to Mobile software or use Mobile software in order to provide sharing use for any third party as well; (iii) make any copy of Mobile software; (iv) remove, avoid, switch off, harm or by any other means influence on Mobile software functional or (v) remove the copyrights notification and any other property rights for Mobile software. The Client agrees to the fact the Company from time to time might release updated versions of Mobile software and may automatically update the web version of Mobile software which are installed on the mobile device. The Clients agrees to the possibility of autoupdates performance on the mobile device as well as to the fact that the terms of present Agreement are to be applied for all kinds of such updates. Any other software that is developed by a third party and might be integrated to Mobile software is distributed on the open license basis or by means of an external client agreement unless otherwise is specified in the terms of Mobile software use. The Company reserves the rights not specified in the present Agreement.  4. Feedback  Upon the providing of e-mail address and cellphone number to the Company, the Client agrees to the fact that the Company uses e-mail address or phone number in order to send notifications regarding the services including any kind of other notifications, claims required by the laws instead of sending paper letters via post. The Company also reserves the right to use the registered e-mail address to send other notifications regarding the Service functional changes and special offers. In case the Client does not want to receive advertisement messages via e-mail the Client is able to disable the mailing option. Please note that the disabling of mailing option might cause the lack of information such as the notification regarding updates, modifications or offers.  5. Our proprietary rights  Apart from the User generated content, the Service, all materials and information specified in it or the data which is generated, collected or transferred by means of the Service or Mobile software use, pictures, text, design, illustrations, logos, patents, trademarks, service marks, copyrights, photos, audio files, videos, music and user content which belong to other users and the rights related to intellectual property are the exclusive ownership of the Company and its licensors (including other Users who allocate the User content for the Service). Except in cases o  f explicit in the present agreement nothing in the present Agreement must be considered as the license creation, therefore the Client agrees not to sell, reproduce, share, demonstrate or execute publicly, publish, adopt, modify or perform dereliction work of any kind of Content. The Company’s Content use for any purposes which not allowed by the present Agreement are strictly prohibited.   10. Indemnification and liability  You agree on indemnifying the Company for losses caused by the violating the terms of this Agreement, including but not limited to, the violating of any statements and warranties specified here; the violation of any third-party rights, including but not limited to the right on privacy or intellectual property rights, the violation of any applicable law or regulation; access to any other party and use of the Service using the unique username, password or other appropriate security code.  12. General provisions  This Agreement and any rights and licenses granted upon this Agreement may not be transferred by you'
                android:textColor="#292150" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>